- In the criminal justice
system.
sexually based offenses
are considered
especially heinous.
In New York City.
the dedicated detectives
who investigate
these vicious felonies
are members of an elite squad
known as
the Special Victims Unit.
These are their stories.
- This one was supposed
to be done hours ago.
- Let the front desk
deal with it.
- Housekeeping.
They'll just say we didn't try.
Housekeeping.
- The lead down to six.
78-72.
Washington.
We'll slow this down.
- That's allowed New York back
into this game.
Walt pounds it with the left.
now gives--
- Hello?
Housekeeping.
- He closes off right side.
tied up.
In the big bodies.
Goes baseline to Arnold
who drives it--
- Call 911!
- What? Why?
What's wrong?
- Good evening. Katie.
- Detectives. good to see you.
- This a drowning?
We hear that right?
- Attempted.
EMTs resuscitated the vic.
rushed him over to Sinai.
- Okay.
Any idea how he's doing?
- Above my pay grade.
But if I were you guys.
I wouldn't hold my breath.
Sorry. that's not what I meant.
- Don't worry about it.
- Bound and dumped in a tub.
You ever seen
anything like this?
- Nope.
This is a first.
- Lucky us.
- Front desk said that
he checked in under John Smith.
and he paid cash.
- All right. so pseudonym.
skeevy hotel with hourly rates.
- You think our vic was a pro?
- Or the client.
- It fits with the booze.
oil. condoms.
and a healthy amount of coke.
- Okay. so party gone wrong?
- No wallet. no phone.
- All right. let's get unis
to canvass the neighborhood.
pull footage.
I mean. there's always a chance
that they dumped it nearby.
- Okay. hang on a second.
Hang on.
We got party favors.
Zip ties. a box cutter.
and a snub nose.
- Oh. so somebody brought
a kill bag to the party.
- Which suggests that it wasn't
a crime of passion.
- Yeah. but why leave
the bag behind?
The vic wasn't stabbed or shot.
- Maybe the perp got excited.
panicked.
- Unless--unless
it wasn't his bag.
- Well. whose ever stuff
this is.
there is something seriously
wrong with 'em.
- Wow.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- Hey. any luck
IDing the victim?
- Yeah. Ian Larkin. age 37.
His fingerprints lit up SAFIS.
He's a repeat customer.
He's got multiple priors for
prostitution. drug possession.
He's been in and out
of the system since he was 18.
- Including a 90-day
stint last year.
- Any idea where he was living?
- Last known address
in the Lower East Side.
but the building came
down in September.
- We did find a family address
out in South Orange. though.
- Okay.
So Rollins and I could
head there in the morning.
talk to the family.
- Want me to swing by
Mount Sinai on my way home?
- You know what?
Sorry. One sec.
Benson.
Mm-hmm.
Oh. Okay.
Yeah. thanks.
Well. there's no need for
you to stop by the hospital.
- Ian?
- Dead.
He never regained
consciousness.
So I want to hang
onto this case.
I'm going to call
Homicide myself.
They're short staffed. so I'm
sure they won't mind the help.
Why don't you head to
the ME's office in the morning
and see if you can find out
what really happened to Ian.
- Should we start with
the drugs found in the room?
- It's your show. Doc.
- Well. it wasn't cocaine.
- Really? Meth?
- Benzos.
- So the perp drugged Ian.
knocked him out.
- Wrong again.
Tox screen was negative.
Mr. Larkin was clean.
Turns out he was
rendered unconscious
the old-fashioned way.
- Cracked on the head.
- Hotel lamp.
After that.
the victim was restrained
with the zip ties. deep cuts.
- Meaning Ian struggled.
- And then the killer strangled
him underwater in the bathtub.
Note the bruising
around the neck.
- I thought Ian was alive when
the cleaning staff found him.
- Best guess. he suffered
a hypoxic blackout
while being strangled.
stopped struggling. and sank.
- Killer assumed he was dead.
- And after they left.
Ian regained consciousness.
poor guy.
- So he was just stuck
in that bathtub?
For how long?
- Judging by his skin
maceration. hours.
- How are we with DNA?
- Lousy. literally.
Bargain-bin hotel
means we've got
samples coming out our ears.
loads of cross-contamination.
We'll run it all. but--
- Needle in a haystack.
- Just about.
- Ian was a good kid. kind.
had his mother's smarts.
thank God.
He could have done anything
he set his mind to.
- Were the two of you close.
Louis?
- I suppose.
Looking back.
maybe there are things
I should have done better with.
- I think it always is
easier in hindsight. right?
When was the last time
you saw Ian?
- He was--
I think he was
here this morning.
Did you get to see him?
- How long has he
been like this?
- He's going on two years now.
went downhill after Ma died.
another gift from Ian.
- Yeah.
Families tend to bear
the brunt of addiction.
- Yeah. well. my brother
was definitely
the kind of junkie who used
and manipulated people.
our folks. most of all.
They lost their savings
because of him.
- That's terrible.
- Yeah.
Ma had to go back to work.
67 years old.
put her in an early grave.
- When did Ian start using?
As long as I can remember.
He started in high school.
never looked back.
- Louis. did Ian ever
talk about his friends
or other people in his life?
- I think he should
be home soon.
School will be letting out.
- Okay.
- It's almost a relief
that Ian's dead.
to know we don't have to pay
for his mistakes anymore.
I guess that
makes me a bad person.
- No. it makes you human.
Listen. do you happen to know
where Ian was living?
- Yeah. unfortunately.
he conned a check
out of my dad last month.
Let me find you the address.
- It's a pretty
bleak existence.
- Yeah. Welcome to the life
of an addict.
We got supplements.
steroids. syringes.
Got some crystal here.
- Hey. I found a tablet.
Battery's dead.
Maybe we can pull
some emails or texts.
- It looks like Ian went
shopping.
bundle of zip ties.
empty packaging
for a box knife.
- Oh. hey.
Hey. look at this. some
bowls of crushed-up pills.
Put money on
them being benzos.
- If Ian is the one who
brought that bag to the hotel.
what was the plan?
- Kink gone wrong?
Rob the John?
- Something went sideways.
- We are left with
a boatload of questions.
- We might have
an answer to one of them.
This is where Ian was
the day he died.
Pro fighter expo--I gotta say.
this is a new one for me.
- Ian was a man of culture.
- All right. let's split up
and see if we can find
somebody who recognizes Ian.
What's that face?
- That's Buffalo Joe.
That's Hawk Hawkins
right there.
That's Chris "The Scary"
Finnerty.
- What's going on here?
- I'm a fan. all right?
When I was a kid.
I used to watch
these fights with my uncle.
He'd splurge on a pay-per-view.
We'd stay up late
on a Saturday night.
And we'd eat a bunch
of junk food. we'd watch it.
Beat the snot out
of each other.
It was great.
- All right.
all right. fan boy.
Let's keep the questions
to the case.
- Okay. no promises.
- Oh. and don't ask
for too many autographs.
- Excuse me.
Hi.
Captain Olivia Benson
with the NYPD.
- I didn't do it.
- I just need a moment
of your time.
- Okay. hon. you are barking
up the absolute right tree.
Yeah. I'm always happy
to support the babes in blue.
- Well. thank you.
I appreciate that.
I'm wondering if
you've seen this man.
He might have been
in two days ago.
- You know what I have seen?
- What?
- I've seen that you got a
spectacular set of baby browns.
- Well. thank you.
That's very kind of you.
- And those yams
aren't bad either.
- Okay.
- Big. big money with sticks
like that in this line of work.
- Noted.
- You know. I think crowds
really go for Amazonian broads.
I think it's a dominance thing.
But how's your right hook?
- It's actually not bad.
- I bet it's pretty good.
- Yeah.
Can I--
have you seen this man?
- Huh.
I don't know.
Maybe. maybe not.
I do know that
my time is valuable.
- Really?
All right. well.
could have fooled me.
- Okay. all right.
I like them spicy.
If you're a little
low on funding.
we can make some
kind of arrangement.
You know. I know my way around
a pair of handcuffs.
if that floats your boat.
- Well. that's tempting.
But I think today.
I'm going to--
I'm going to stick with cash.
Will that do it for you?
- It'll do something.
- Have you--
- Yes. I've seen your fella.
He was here on the day
the expo opened.
- Okay.
Did you speak with him?
- Tried to sell him
a photo. half price.
and the prick turned me down.
I mean. who--in what world?
-All right.
Did you--did you happen to
notice. was he with anyone?
- I didn't notice. no.
- Did you notice
where he went after?
- Same place as everybody else.
to see the headliner.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you very. very much.
- Deuce. keep these folks
in one line. will you?
And make sure they have cash.
- Excuse me.
Do you mind if I take
a peek at that?
- Oh. yeah. sure.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Oh.
I can't say the kid
looks familiar.
- He would have
been here on Friday.
- I mean. it's possible.
but I've seen a lot
of folks this weekend.
And unfortunately.
the old memory
ain't what it used to be.
- Occupational hazard?
- 40 years of taking
shots to the dome.
- Yeah. I got to ask.
what's with the mask?
- Oh. intimidation.
Walk out to the ring
wearing something like that.
you get in the other guy's head
before you even thrown a punch.
Plus. the fans go nuts.
- Mm.
- Everybody loves a character.
80 bucks. made in the USA.
- You keep
the credit card receipts?
- Cash only.
Uncle Sam gets sticky
fingers otherwise.
- Yeah. well. what about--
what about the photos
that you take with fans?
You have any digital copies?
- Polaroids.
I'm old-school.
I feel like I'm kind
of striking out for you guys.
Wish I were more help.
- We're used to it--
occupational hazard.
- I have to ask you where
you were on Friday night.
- Sure.
We wrapped up here and then--
that's right.
And then Sharon and I.
we spent the night
with a couple
of the bruiser fight guys.
Oh. speaking of--
- Sorry. I'm Sharon Huntsinger.
Clint's agent.
The crowd's getting restless.
I really need him back.
- Okay. well. thank you so much
for your time. Mr. O'Neill.
And if there's anything
that you do think of.
or anything comes back--
- Oh. yeah.
Clint. And I will.
Who knows?
Maybe something
will shake loose.
- Great.
Thank you.
- Hey. Cap.
- Mm.
- So off this new lens
of professional fighting.
we pulled the paper archives.
found a mention of Ian
in "The Post" back in 2002.
- "Local boys looking
for a fight."
- Yeah. so the article
talks about Ian
and these other teen superfans.
the Bruiser Fighting
Championship.
It's kind of like a local MMA
precursor. got real popular.
They would hold these
Tough Dude Tournaments. right.
basically. like
legalized street fights.
real big personalities.
very few rules.
boxers like O'Neill.
judo guys. grapplers.
And they'd all try
to kill each other.
It got real brutal. real brutal
knockouts. lots of blood.
- And you would watch
this with your uncle?
- Yeah.
Oh. yeah.
Yeah. we loved it.
It was amazing.
We weren't
the only ones. either.
Ian. these other kids.
they were--
they were. like. obsessed.
never missed a bout.
And they'd hang out so much.
some of these fighters would
get to know them.
They would take them
under their wing.
- Hey. TARU was able to pull
some emails from Ian's tablet.
And one in particular
stands out.
The day before
Ian was murdered.
he got this email from
a user named Razor Crazor.
- "Keep your mouth shut.
You tell anyone about us.
and I'll effing kill you."
- Razor.
Oh. yeah. here it is.
Okay. here's a photo
of Ian back in 2002
with another kid
named Roddy "Razor" Ray.
- Yo. Razor. good fight. man.
- Appreciate it. kid.
- Hey. you're Roddy Ray?
- It's Razor.
Why?
- We're police.
We want to talk to you
about Ian Larkin.
- Yeah. I don't have
anything to say about him.
- Oh. yeah?
Why's that?
- Because the dude is a
crackhead who can't be trusted.
- Is that why you
threatened him?
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- "Keep your mouth shut.
or I'll kill you"?
Sounds pretty
threatening to me.
- Yeah. me too.
- So where were you
last Friday night?
- Home. half a case deep.
Why?
- Because Ian Larkin is dead.
- You know anything
about that. Razor?
How'd you get those scratches?
- Did you not just see us jack
each other up in the ring?
- Yeah. I know.
But they could be from
a different kind of fight.
- Do you mind telling
us why you wanted
Ian to keep his mouth shut?
- It's private.
- Okay.
We can keep a secret.
- I said it's none
of your business.
- Hey. buddy why
don't you calm down?
- Do not touch me!
No.
- Not your best move.
- I said not to touch me.
- Get your hands
behind your back.
- It doesn't matter how
many times you guys ask.
I didn't kill Ian.
- We heard you.
But there's still an issue
of you not having an alibi.
- Well. not to mention you
threatening to kill Ian.
- I didn't mean it like that.
- Okay.
How did you mean it?
- You never told
one of your friends
you were going to kill him?
I mean. I've known
the kid for a long time.
- All right. so you two met
as fans of the Bruiser fights.
So tell me about that.
- It was fine.
Good. I guess.
- Spend a lot of time
with the fighters?
- Yeah. every chance we could--
after an event.
in the gym. wherever.
I mean. we wanted to learn.
So you did what they told you.
And maybe some of the guys
took it a little too far.
but they were stars.
That's just the way it was.
- And Ian?
- Soft.
Yeah. he couldn't
handle things.
- Like. what kind of things?
- Being messed with.
- Okay. well. that's
a lot of responsibility
for a teenage boy. right.
who's hanging out
with their idols.
guys that were heroes to them.
- It's also an easy way for
kids to get taken advantage of.
- You ever see that happen?
You know. Razor.
childhood victims often carry
the weight of the abuse. right?
They carry the shame.
But the only one that
should feel shame
are the adults
that betrayed them.
the adults that failed them.
- You know. at first.
it was like a dream.
getting to watch
those guys train and fight.
You get close to them.
you know.
maybe share a couple drinks.
smoke some pot.
- It makes you feel
older. important?
- Yeah.
That line gets blurred.
- One of them starts getting
physical and touching.
It felt gross.
- So that's what predators do.
They make things that
should feel really scary.
they make those things normal.
Can you tell us his name.
your abuser?
- Clint.
Clint O'Neill.
- And you could come forward
and hold O'Neill accountable
for what he did.
- Screw that.
I'd be a joke.
I'm not about to throw
my career away for this.
- Razor. you spend Sunday
nights at a VFW.
bleeding
for a few dozen people.
What are you really losing?
- This doesn't seem
like much to you.
but fighting.
this is the only thing that
I have ever been good at.
- I don't understand.
He--he had never said anything
to me or to our parents.
- So it's very common
for victims of sexual abuse.
- Especially young men.
- I--I resented him.
I treated him like
he was a burden.
Oh. my God.
what's wrong with me?
I was so relieved when
I found out he was dead.
- Shawn. you didn't know.
- Well. I should have.
I'm his brother.
If I had seen something.
I could have helped.
- You can't think like that.
- It's my fault.
I got him into
all that fight crap.
Buds of mine used to hang
around those shows.
- Do you remember
any of their names?
- Probably.
- Okay. well. we would
love to take a look
at Ian's belongings. if you
have any of them in case--
- Yeah. yeah.
Ian got off probation last year
and moved in with Dad and me.
And Ian left most
of his stuff behind.
- Oh.
- Yeah. I get it.
Okay. thanks.
- Didn't go well?
- I spoke with Shawn's
high school friends.
All three spent lots
of time with the fighters.
including O'Neill.
One moved away.
refuses to talk to me.
The other insists.
never saw anything.
- And the third?
- Jumped off a bridge
ten years ago.
- Okay. so O'Neill's alibi
is holding up.
He had dinner with
Sharon Huntsinger. his agent.
and two other people.
And the GPS from his phone
shows that he went
straight back to his hotel.
which was clear across town
from where Ian was found.
- All right.
So if it is O'Neill.
we're going to need
more to connect him to Ian.
- Well. we went through
Ian's belongings.
It's mostly junk.
But we found a journal
from around 2005.
He--he writes about
the abuse in detail.
locations where it happened.
specific acts that he was
forced to be engaged in.
He even talks about
how he blamed himself.
But he never names
O'Neill outright.
- Also turned up records
of a payment Ian received
around the same time
for a whopping 1.200 bucks.
labeled as "reimbursement
for expenses."
- He signed an agreement
for that money.
one with confidentiality.
non-disparagement clauses.
and release of any claim
to litigation.
- Who was the agreement with?
- A defunct LLC called
Fight Reps. Incorporated.
owned by Sharon Huntsinger.
- His agent.
- Yeah.
- Makes this interesting.
- Correspondence
with a law firm.
- From last year.
Ian wanted to sue
Sharon and O'Neill.
- According
to the lawyer's notes.
Huntsinger flipped out
when the firm contacted
her over a potential suit.
- So maybe if Ian
popped up recently.
she wanted to keep him quiet.
- Or cover it up.
Look. I am going to give
Sharon a little squeeze
and see just how loyal
she is to her favorite client.
- I'd be lying if I said
the fight game was easy.
People would rather
watch inbreds slap
each other on the internet.
But I managed to keep
the place afloat.
Might not be
fancy offices on Park Ave.
but my guys know I'm dedicated.
- Well. you certainly
go the extra mile.
- Clients love
a personal touch.
- That's curious phrasing.
considering that Clint O'Neill
sexually abuses teenage boys.
- The hell he does.
That's a ridiculous claim.
I never heard such a thing.
- Come on. Sharon.
We know that you paid
a settlement
to Ian Larkin on behalf
of Clint over 20 years ago.
- Two decades. I'm supposed
to know who that person is?
- Well. you had multiple
conversations with Ian's lawyer
about a potential lawsuit.
I have all the records
to prove it.
So. yeah. I expect you
to know who that is.
- Okay. yeah. maybe that
name sounds familiar.
You don't understand.
I know Clint.
He isn't capable of that.
- What makes you so sure?
- Clint's more than
just my client.
He's like family.
stuck with me. thick and thin.
And some drug addict from years
back wants to ruin his legacy?
I can't have that.
- That sounds like
motive for murder.
- What do you--
what do you mean?
- Well. Ian's dead.
He was killed opening night
of the convention.
So tell me.
what happened. Sharon?
Were you scared he was
gonna make a scene. right?
Ruin the whole business?
- You can't think
that I would ever--
- You said it yourself.
you had to protect
Clint's legacy.
- Yeah. but I couldn't
overpower a man--
- You could. if he was
incapacitated. couldn't you?
- Clint didn't go back
to his hotel after dinner.
- Where did he go?
- I'm not sure.
He said he wanted to take
a stroll around the city.
After I paid the bill.
I saw Clint left his phone
on the table.
I brought it back to his hotel.
I left it with the front desk.
and I didn't see
Clint until morning.
- Are you sick and tired
of dishonest salesmen
and double talk?
Then come on down
to Kennedy Motors.
where we shoot straight.
And dirty tricks end
up where they belong--
--out with the trash.
- Cut.
Great job. Clint.
Steph. let's take
the shine off that can.
- Mr. O'Neill.
we'd like for you
to come downtown.
answer some questions.
- You guys can see
I'm busy. right?
We can talk another time.
- No. it's best
for all involved
if you straighten this out now.
- Everything okay. Clint?
- Yeah. Yep.
Just give me a second.
- Or if you'd rather.
Clint. we can explain
to these nice people
how much you like
diddling teenage boys.
- Jason. Powell. I'm so sorry.
My calendar got crossed.
We're gonna have to
pick this up tomorrow.
- Wait. what?
- No. I'll see you tomorrow.
- So. Clint.
your alibi fell apart.
We know that you didn't
go back to your hotel.
- Pretty shrewd move.
leaving your phone.
- It's a mistake.
I told you. memory
ain't what it once was.
So I got turned around on
the way back to the hotel.
Is that a crime?
- Okay. so the
problem with that is
that we have you on camera
one block from where
Ian Larkin was murdered.
- I must have walked
further than I thought.
- And you lied about
not knowing Ian Larkin.
- Come on. Clint. it's
pretty hard to forget someone
that you sexually abused.
not to mention somebody that
you had your agent pay off
to cover for you.
- Do you have any idea
the nonsense people have
made up about me
over the years?
It's the cost
of doing business.
But everybody wants
a piece of the champ.
- Piece of the champ.
So you're saying that
you're the victim here?
- I ain't the villain.
I'll tell you that.
- Okay. well.
let's say that that's true.
and you didn't intend
for any of this to happen.
I mean. we know that Ian came
to you with bad intentions.
We know that he had zip ties.
He had drugs.
He had a gun.
- Maybe you did just
want to talk. but Ian--
Ian threatened you.
attacked you.
and caught you off guard.
Maybe he was
trying to hurt you.
And that would be
self-defense. right?
- It certainly is.
And if it is self-defense.
in that case. then we can--
we can help you.
But if we're gonna help you.
we need to know the truth.
- Yeah.
Yeah. maybe there's a story
I can lay out. where. uh.
this junkie tried to get
one over on me.
thinks I'm too old.
that I lost a step.
This paper-thin twerp thought
I was stupid.
like I couldn't see his game a
mile away.
tried to put hands on me.
so I smacked him a couple
of times. just a warning.
give him a chance to walk away.
But he keeps coming.
Crying and whining.
Pathetic.
But you know.
guys like that don't learn.
You got to teach them.
show them there's a cost
for coming at the big dog.
And you know what?
I think the kid got it.
I think the kid finally
learned his lesson.
right there at the end.
just as the light left
his eyes.
That what you were
hoping to hear?
Hmm?
Because it's nonsense.
stuff I'd say
to hype up a fight.
But that's an act.
It's a gimmick.
Sure. I might talk like
a killer for the fans.
but it's just that.
It's talk.
And I'm pretty sure you
don't have the evidence
to prove otherwise.
So if it's all the same.
I'd like my lawyer.
- Well. that was
quite the performance.
- Yeah.
O'Neill may be crazy. but
he's good at playing a role.
- And he's going to use
it to his advantage.
I mean. he's charismatic.
He's good with a crowd.
- Not the kind of person
you want in front of a jury.
They'll eat him up.
- Which means we need more.
What about other victims?
- We tried.
But between it being
so long ago
and there being no real
record of these boys.
I mean. we came up empty.
- Well. either we tie O'Neill
directly to Ian or he walks.
- Razor.
- I already gave my answer.
- I know. I know.
- I'm not changing my mind.
- I know.
- Then what?
What are we doing here?
Because I'm on the clock.
- All right. so I--
I found one of Ian's journals.
And I thought you should
read one of his entries.
Just read it.
- "I'm just tired of it all.
putting on a face.
"going through the motions.
waking up every day.
"And if it weren't for--
- Keep reading.
Look.
"If it weren't for Razor.
"I would have checked out
a long time ago
"because I can't leave him
alone.
"It's just us.
"No one else understands.
"They don't get it. but we do.
"And if I give up. then
the guy who hurts us wins.
And that would piss off
Razor more than anything."
- That's a cheap shot. lady.
- Maybe.
But it's the truth.
And I wish that it weren't
the case. but it is.
Razor. if you
don't come forward.
then O'Neill gets
away with everything.
everything that he did to you
and everything he did to Ian.
- The state of the room.
along with extensive
subdermal bruising
on the victim's arms and torso.
points to a violent struggle.
- Ian Larkin fought back.
- Yes.
Unfortunately.
a basilar skull fracture led
to a number
of intracranial hematomas.
Those. along with extensive
damage to the victim's larynx.
would indicate that he suffered
greatly before he died.
- Do these injuries
on Mr. Larkin
tell you anything
about his attacker?
- Laryngeal trauma this
severe requires a person
of significant strength.
- Someone like Mr. O'Neill?
- Yes.
- No further questions.
- Ms. Horowitz. is my client
the only person
of significant strength
in the New York area?
- Probably not.
- Do you know how many
strong individuals were
in Manhattan at the time
of Mr. Larkin's death?
- No. I couldn't say.
- Fair enough.
Could you say how many unique
DNA samples you recovered
at the scene of the crime?
- 34.
- And of the 34. did any
match Mr. O'Neill's DNA?
- They did not.
- Tell me. did
the NYPD even bother
with those other suspects?
Or had they already decided
my client was guilty?
- Objection.
Argumentative.
- Withdrawn.
Thank you. Ms. Horowitz.
- Do you swear to tell
the truth. the whole truth.
and nothing but the truth?
- I do.
- Mr. Ray. when did you first
meet Ian Larkin?
- I was 15.
We were both
Bruiser fight fans.
Honestly. I didn't really
like Ian at first
because he was
sort of a know-it-all.
But we bonded.
became fast friends.
- And then the two of
you started spending time
with some of the fighters.
- Yeah.
They kind of took
us under their wing.
Some were great guys.
and we got to train
with the best in the business.
- Mr. Ray. I know
this is difficult.
but could you tell the court
when the sexual abuse
first started?
- No. I can't.
- I'm sorry?
- I was never sexually abused.
- Mr. Ray. previously. you told
detectives that you had been
molested by Clint O'Neill.
- Yeah. that never happened.
- I remind you.
you're under oath.
- I know.
- So when you told Captain
Benson that the defendant had
groomed you. plied you
with alcohol and drugs.
and touched you sexually.
that was a lie?
- Yeah.
- And when you told them
that you believed
Clint O'Neill killed
Ian Larkin--
- I was lying.
- Or you're lying now.
- Mr. Carisi.
- Mr. Ray. why would
you lie to the police?
- They said Ian was dead.
I felt terrible.
I told them what I thought
they wanted to hear.
But being here now in
the court. I can't do it.
I gotta tell the truth.
- Hey. Ray.
Closing doors in 45. okay?
- Yeah.
- I just saw
Sharon Huntsinger outside. huh?
I'm assuming she's
here to see you.
- She might have said hello.
She's a fan of my work.
- Ah. is that what
you're going with?
- Why is that so
hard to believe?
- What'd she give you?
What?
- Contract to be a client.
She's going to book
me some gigs in Japan.
- Was it worth it?
Was it?
- What do you want me to say?
- I want you to tell me how you
can let someone like O'Neill
get away with
what they did to you.
with what they did to Ian.
- Ian is gone. all right?
I'm here.
I've been living
with this for 20 years.
Do you know what I have
to show for it?
Pain. poverty.
These. this is it.
Clock's running out.
It's my last chance.
And you know what?
If Ian were here.
he'd understand.
- I feel bad for what
happened to that kid.
I do.
But I didn't know him.
And I had nothing
to do with his death.
- Why do you think
Mr. Larkin was fixated on you?
- Well. I can't say for sure.
but I've been fighting
a long time.
lots of states.
lots of cities.
And everywhere I went.
people always wanted
something from me.
wanted me to be their hero.
their dad. their teacher.
But in this case.
I suppose I'm their monster.
But they got the wrong guy.
- Nothing further.
- You good at your job.
Mr. O'Neill?
- I'm a ten-time champ.
You tell me.
- How many of those belts were
in professional boxing?
- Two.
- And since then.
you've fought exclusively
for Bruiser Fighting
Championship. correct?
- Yep. bigger
and better things.
- It wasn't because
you were permanently banned
from boxing in 1992.
accused of taking a dive.
if I'm not mistaken?
- If you say so.
- Well. to be fair.
I'm not saying that.
That's every sanctioning
body in pro boxing.
the WBC. the IBF. the WBA.
- Your point is?
- Well. Mr. O'Neill.
I just find it interesting
that you claim success because
of your skill in the ring.
But who's to say. given
your history of cheating.
that any of your fights
were on the level?
I mean. doesn't it call into
question your entire career?
- No.
I wouldn't say that.
- Of course you
wouldn't say that.
You've got a legacy to protect.
But to the rest of us.
your willingness to lie.
to betray the sport
that supposedly you care
so much about--
- I have given my life
to this business.
- But who's to say any
of your fights were real?
All your knockouts. your wins--
how do we know that those guys
weren't taking dives for you?
- You wouldn't last ten seconds
with the men I faced.
- Oh. please.
We all know you
don't fight real men.
- Is that so?
- Objection. Badgering.
- No. no. You're out hurting
teenage boys.
- Sustained.
Mr. Carisi.
- Shut your mouth.
- Is that what you tell
the children you molest?
- Enough.
Do you have any pertinent
questions left. Mr. Carisi?
- No. Your Honor.
I have nothing further.
- As to the count of
murder in the second degree.
how do you find?
- We find the defendant
not guilty.
- Ladies and gentlemen.
I know this has been
a lengthy and
difficult deliberation.
Personally.
along with the State.
I thank you for your service.
- Hey. I know that it's not
the verdict that we wanted.
so let's take the night
to be pissed.
But tomorrow morning.
we start to build a new case.
- O'Neill was acquitted. boss.
- Of murder.
not of sexual assault.
- Do you really think
we can get enough on him
without Ian or Razor?
- I think that Clint O'Neill
has been out there.
He's been a predator
for a very long time.
There has to be other victims.
We just need to find them.
- It's going to be
an uphill battle.
- Yeah. so we widen the net.
We talk to every
single person that
has crossed paths
with Clint O'Neill
in the last 20 years.
But we do whatever it takes.
- The fight goes on.
- Captain Benson.
message for you.
- Thank you.
Excuse me.
Hey.
- Old fella was jumped
as he left the diner.
stabbed to death.
choked on his own blood.
Rough way to go.
- Is the attacker in custody?
- Back of the squad car.
- Shawn?
- I had to do something.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm